tuneskit.com 2019-11-12

# Tuneskit Privacy Policy

TunesKit is committed to protecting your privacy so we will only collect your personal information for defined purposes. We do not distribute or share your personal information beyond what is strictly necessary to fulfill our obligations to you. We may share your information only with partners who adhere to TunesKit's commitment to protecting your privacy. TunesKit will not sell your personal information in any manner whatsoever.

### What information do we collect? What do we use it for?

When you place an order on our website, your full name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card number, and credit card expiration date will be required. The information is used to complete the transaction and help us provide better support and services to you.

### How do the 3rd party credit card processors protect your private information?

TunesKit uses secure server hosted by FastSpring credit card processor that encrypt all the customer's personal information before sent to us, including name, address, credit card number, credit card expiration date, etc. Encryption works to prevent any malicious use of your personal information. Your credit card information is only used for online transition.

### FastSpring

FastSpring was founded in 2005 as a partnership of industry veterans with over 40 years experience in the e-commerce software industry, with a vision of bypassing legacy systems, addressing e-commerce customer dissatisfaction and building a robust e-commerce engine with the latest database, transactional and marketing technologies. We use FastSpring to provide you with very secure and fast online purchase.

### About cookies and other similar technologies

In order to better understand what services are valuable to our customers, we use "cookies". A cookie is a small text file that a Website writes to your hard drive. Cookies work as your identification card and may record passwords, preferences and purchases. Cookies let the web page server know that you have returned to this site. Cookies also can determine other information, such as the daily visitors to our website and the pages of the site most frequently visited. Cookies are unique and can only be read by the server that assigns them. They cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.

Similar technologies that are used to store information in your browser or device internal storage include HTML 5 cookies, flash cookies, and other web or mobile application methods.

### How to block cookies

If you do not want to have a cookie set when visiting our webiste, you can change the settings in your browser as instructed below to prevent cookies. However, by doing so, you may not have full access to all the web pages. These are the guides on how to disable cookies on some widely used browsers:

Safari: [how to delete and disable cookies on Safari](https://support.apple.com/kb/ph21411)

Chrome: [how to delete cookies on Google Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647)

Edge: [how to disable cookies on Microsoft Edge](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy)

Firefox: [how to delete cookies on Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences)

IE: [how to disable cookies on Internet Explorer](http://windows.microsoft.com/en-us/internet-explorer/delete-manage-cookies)

### Updates to TunesKit privacy policy

TunesKit reserves the rights to modify this privacy policy from time to time without noticing you in advance. Any update or modification becomes applicable immediately once published. You are highly suggested to review this page every now and then so that you can be aware of our latest policies on privacy and collection of your private info.

_This privacy policy was last updated on June 25, 2018._
